[
    {
        "question": "What major river runs through Melbourne?",
        "answer": "Yarra"
    },
    {
        "question": "What major river runs through Buenos Aires Province?",
        "answer": "Rio de la Plata"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find `Peachtree Street`?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the largest landlocked country in Europe?",
        "answer": "Belarus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest of the Spanish Balearic islands?",
        "answer": "Majorca"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most visited attraction in New York City?",
        "answer": "The Metropolitan Museum of Art"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US city can you find `Bubblegum Alley`?",
        "answer": "San Luis Obispo, California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Italian city is considered the birthplace of modern gelato?",
        "answer": "Florence"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wichita Mountains can be found in which U.S. state?",
        "answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Karakum desert occupies 70% of what country?",
        "answer": "Turkmenistan -- Turkmenistan lies on the eastern coast of the Caspian Sea, but a majority of the country is covered by the Karakum Desert."
    },
    {
        "question": "What three countries intersect at Mount Roraima?",
        "answer": "Venezuela, Brazil, and Guyana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is connected to the most countries by land?",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "French is the official language for how many nations?",
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "`Chili crab` is a dish from which country?",
        "answer": "Singapore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freetown is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Sierra Leone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freetown is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Sierra Leone"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city will you find the Tiergarten Park?",
        "answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamaica is considered part of which continent?",
        "answer": "North America"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pago Pago is the capital of which country",
        "answer": "American Samoa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the last Province to join Canada?",
        "answer": "Newfoundland and Labrador"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Viking settlement known as Jarlshof is located where?",
        "answer": "Shetland Islands, Scotland -- This ancient Viking settlement is packed with 4,000 years of history."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you hike a 1800-mile-long trail that spans an entire country?",
        "answer": "New Zealand -- The Araroa, which translates to \u201cThe Long Path,\u201d is a hiking trail that runs the length of the country."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two rivers form much of the border between the U.S. states Minnesota and Wisconsin?",
        "answer": "Mississippi River and St. Croix River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which archipelago is known in Spanish as Islas Malvinas?",
        "answer": "Falkland Islands -- It is an archipelago of about 200 islands located roughly 300 miles from the southern tip of South America."
    },
    {
        "question": "What split up into Gondwanaland and Laurasia?",
        "answer": "Pangaea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Parts of what Chilean desert have gone four hundred years without rainfall?",
        "answer": "The Atacama"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only US state with a Union Jack on its flag?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first cash crop in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Tobacco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Kingdom is Greenland a part of?",
        "answer": "The Kingdom of Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "What wild horse can be found on beaches in Virginia and Maryland?",
        "answer": "Chincoteague -- They are a breed of wild horses that live on the beaches of Assateague Island off the coast of Maryland and Virginia."
    },
    {
        "question": "What body of water in Australia was once called Stingray Harbour?",
        "answer": "Botany Bay -- Capt. James Cook originally named it, but Joseph Banks, a naturalist, renamed it a few days later after collecting 132 plant specimens."
    },
    {
        "question": "San Francisco`s Nob Hill was named after what?",
        "answer": "Railroad barons -- While it`s no longer a commonly used term, `nabob` is a word borrowed from Hindu that refers to a wealthy or influential person."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has trick-or-treating on Easter?",
        "answer": "Sweden -- The custom is rooted in a tale about witches on broomsticks meeting with the Devil on the legendary island of Bl\u00e5kulla and returning to Sweden the night before Easter."
    },
    {
        "question": "The film `Twilight` was shot at which beach in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Cannon Beach in Oregon -- It`s not a typical sunny and tropical beach, but the beach is still so cinematically beautiful that film scenes are filmed there."
    },
    {
        "question": "The film `Goonies` was shot at which beach in the U.S?",
        "answer": "Cannon Beach in Oregon -- It`s not a typical sunny and tropical beach, but it is still so cinematically beautiful that many film scenes are filmed there."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean is Cook Islands located in?",
        "answer": "Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": "Belgrade lies on the Danube and which other river?",
        "answer": "Sava"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Colorado?",
        "answer": "Denver"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which African nation gained its independence on July 9, 2011?",
        "answer": "South Sudan"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Republic of South Sudan gain its independence?",
        "answer": "July 9, 2011"
    },
    {
        "question": "Athens is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which peninsula is Greece located on?",
        "answer": "Balkan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sea lies west of mainland Greece?",
        "answer": "Ionian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sea lies east of mainland Greece?",
        "answer": "Aegean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Australian state of Tasmania?",
        "answer": "Hobart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hobart is the capital of which Australian state?",
        "answer": "Tasmania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tangier is a coastal town in which Arab country?",
        "answer": "Morocco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s Easter brunch typically includes a ryemeal soup known as zurek?",
        "answer": "Poland"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find Mont-Saint-Michel?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Casa Rosada?",
        "answer": "Argentina"
    }
]